# **NIK SANKOVICH**

1730 E. Oltorf St - Austin, Tx 78741 - (210)585-0662 - Nik.sankovich@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Sales professional with a strong technical background and sales experience in high-pressure environments. Key strengths include building and maintaining client relationships, exceeding sales quotas, and presenting to target prospects. Excellent communicator and fast learner, able to quickly adapt to emerging challenges while meeting the needs of customers.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Salesforce	Java	Excel	LinkedIn
Outreach	С	Powerpoint	Word

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2022 Spycloud Austin, Tx

Sales Development Representative

- Managed book of business of over 500 accounts to generate pipeline for Account Executives
- Utilized tools such as Outreach and Salesforce to exceed daily KPI's consistently
- Achieved 100% of sales quota in June and July of 2022
- Participated in discovery calls and product demonstrations alongside Account Executives

2021 - 2022 Dialpad Austin, Tx

Sales Development Representative - Mid-Market

- Built and managed a pipeline of leads using CRM software such as Salesforce and Outreach
- Achieved 100% of sales quota in December and January of 2021, generating 5 qualified opportunities for Account Executives

2020 - 2021 Brightwheel Austin, Tx

Sales Development Representative

- Generated sales opportunities for Account Executives at a fast paced SaaS startup focusing on early childhood education
- Cold-called and emailed over 80 early childhood education centers per day to achieve sales quotas
- Fostered relationships with key decision-makers at early childhood education centers in order to increase business

2019 - 2020 Arrive Logistics Austin, Tx

National Account Representative - Carrier Sales

- Managed sales for a third-party logistics brokerage, selling 90-100 shipments per month in various verticals and acquiring more than 25 new carrier accounts
- Achieved 137% of sales quota in January 2020, selling 110 shipments, and generated more than \$10K in revenue per month

### **EDUCATION**

.

## **University of Texas at San Antonio**

San Antonio, Tx

Bachelor of Arts, Multidisciplinary Studies - History, Computer Science & Anthropology (2019)